[
  {
    "question": "Which option, when applied to a rule, allows traffic to VPN gateways in specific VPN communities?",
    "options": " A. All Connections (Clear or Encrypted)\n B. Accept all encrypted traffic\n C. Specific VPN Communities}\n D. All Site-to-Site VPN Communities",
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "When configuring Spoof Tracking, which tracking actions can an administrator select to be done when spoofed packets are detected?",
    "options": " A. Log, send snmp trap, email\n B. Drop packet, alert, none\n C. Log, alert, none\n D. Log, allow packets, email",
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Access roles allow the firewall administrator to configure network access according to",
    "options": " A. a combination of computer groups and network\n B. users and user groups\n C. all of above\n D. remote access clients",
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the three deployment considerations for a secure network?",
    "options": " A. Distributed, Bridge Mode, and Remote\n B. Bridge Mode, Remote, and Standalone\n C. Remote, Standalone, and Distributed\n D. Standalone, Distributed, and Bridge Mode",
    "answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following Windows Security Events will NOT map a username to an IP address in Identity Awareness?",
    "options": " A. Kerberos Ticket Renewed\n B. Kerberos Ticket Requested\n C. Account Logon\n D. Kerberos Ticket Timed Out",
    "answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Fill in the blank: Permanent VPN tunnels can be set on all tunnels in the community, on all tunnels for specific gateways, or__________.",
    "options": " A. On all satellite gateway to satellite gateway tunnels\n B. On specific tunnels for specific gateways\n C. On specific tunnels in the community\n D. On specific satellite gateway to central gateway tunnels",
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Unified SmartConsole Gateways and Servers tab you can perform the following functions EXCEPT",
    "options": " A. Upgrade the software version\n B. Open WebUI\n C. Open SSH\n D. Open service request with Check Point Technical Support",
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Threat Prevention Software Blade provides protection from malicious software that can infect your network computers?",
    "options": " A. Anti-Malware\n B. IPS\n C. Anti-bot\n D. Anti-Spam",
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which icon indicates that read/write access is enabled?",
    "options": " A. Pencil\n B. Padlock\n C. Book\n D. Eyeglasses",
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following blades is NOT subscription-based and therefore does not have to be renewed on a regular basis?",
    "options": " A. Application Control\n B. Threat Emulation\n C. Anti-Virus\n D. Advanced Networking Blade",
    "answer": "d"
  }
]
